Come on.
هيا
Has your body degenerated
لقد كنت في العصور القديمة لفترة طويلة
because you've been in this era for too long?
وتراجع جسدك
You use whatever you learned from Master.
استخدم ما علمك المعلم
Don't you make improvements?
لماذا لا تدرس بجد؟
Do you think everyone is like you?
هل تعتقد أن الجميع مثلك
You know you shouldn't do it, but you just won't give up.
يعرف بوضوح أنه لا يمكن فعل ذلك
They stop when they receive the warning.
والآخرون لم يصلوا إلى الخطوة تحذير
Really?
لا أعتقد ذلك
You can't even dodge that?
لا يمكن تجنبه
Again.
مرة أخرى
Go away. It's nothing.
ابتعد ابتعد   لا يوجد شيء جميل
Why didn't you dodge?
لماذا لا تختبئ
What?
ماذا؟
You will go back with me if I dodged?
هل يمكنك العودة معي إذا اختبأت؟
I have to get some evidence to report.
يجب أن أجد بعض الأدلة
You...
أنت
Well.
لا أقصد
Why have you become like an old man
لقد بقيت هنا لفترة طويلة
since you came here?
لماذا أصبحت عجوزًا؟
Well...
هذا
Just say it.
قل ما تريد قوله
Why are you like the people here?
كيف تغيرت مثل القدماء
Dilly-dallying.
متردد
Tell me.
قل
If the future can really change the past,
إذا استطعنا حقا تغيير الماضي
our decisions will be
هل قرارنا
dynamically open
ليس مغلقًا
instead of being closed, right?
بل مفتوح الحركة
And there won't be any wrong choice, right?
ألن يكون هناك اختيار خاطئ
You just
ماذا عنك؟
do whatever you want.
افعل ما تريد
Anyway,
على أي حال
you'll regret no matter what choice you make.
ستندمين على أي خيار
Fate is always intertwined.
على أي حال، القدر دائماً ما يكون هناك خطأ
Hey.
مهلاً
Enough. When do you plan to go back?
حسنًا متى ستعود؟
Soon.
قريبا
Dioscorea nipponica Makino will be mature soon.
ستصبح رقائق البطاطس على الفور
Well,
إذًا
what about the people here?
ماذا عن المعروف؟
I thought
اعتقدت
I could have everything well under control.
يمكنني السيطرة على نفسي بشكل جيد
But
لكن
she has her own ideas, right?
لديها أفكارها الخاصة أليس كذلك
If the ending is destined to be bad,
إذا كان المصير غير جميل
why don't we make the process pleasant?
فلماذا لا تترك أي عملية جميلة
I want to make wonderful memories with her.
أريد أن أحصل على ذكريات جميلة معها
What's wrong with you?
هل أنت مجنون؟
Good luck to you.
اعتني بنفسك
You can keep your passion. But please reduce the speed, okay?
‫يمكن أن يبقى الحماس وتضعي السرعة مؤقتا‬
Or
أم
you can't lift your right foot?
لا يمكنك رفع قدمك اليمنى
If you have a problem, you can drive.
إذا لم تستطيعي القيادة
I'm just fully charged. I haven't recovered yet.
لقد شحنت الكهرباء للتو ولم تتعافى بعد
I opened the gate of time and space for you.
فتحت لك باب الزمان والمكان
But you were in a coma, and I was not charged for three days.
لكنك فقدت الوعي لثلاثة أيام ولم تشحن الكهرباء لي
I thought I was gone.
ظننت أنه بدوني
Just say what you want to say.
قل ما تريد قوله
I'm not like you.
أنا لست مثلك
I don't beat about the bush.
ليس لدي مزاج للدور
That's why Song Yiju and I are good friends.
لذلك أنا صديقة جيدة مع سونغ يي تشنغ
Do you think Ouyang Yu can borrow that trolley?
هل تعتقد أن أويانغ يو سيستعير تلك السيارة
I think he can.
يجب أن يكون بخير
After all, he's so charming.
بعد كل شيء هو النوع من المعجبين
Right.
صحيح
When I first met Wei,
عندما قابلت الأخت وي للتو
she kept pestering me every day.
كان يطاردني كل يوم
How should I repay him?
كيف يمكنني أن أرد لك الجميل؟
He also helped me solve the problem of the comics competition.
لقد ساعدني في حل مسابقة الكرتون
Do you think
أخبريني
I should add an awning to his motorbike
هل يجب أن أضيف استوديو لسيارته
to repay his kindness?
لأرد الجميل له
Are you serious?
هل أنت جاد؟
Are you threatening me?
هل تهددني؟
No. I'm just thinking of a way
لا أنا أفكر في طريقة
to repay your kindness.
كيف أرد الجميل لك
Then go somewhere with me tonight.
إذاً اذهب معي إلى مكان الليلة
Consider it your repayment to me.
اعتبره رد لي الجميل
Okay.
حسنا حسنا
Deliver these food to Wei now.
أرسل هذه الطعام إلى الأخت وي بسرعة
Otherwise, she will be mad at you.
وإلا ستهاجمك الأخت وي
Be careful.
ببطء
Illusion.
هلوسة
It must be an illusion.
لا بد أنها هلوسة
Are you meditating?
لا بد أنها
I saw her.
لقد رأيتها
You saw her?
رأيتها
I didn't see her even with my 12K hawk eyes.
لم أر عيني النسر العالية 12K
It's true that you're the only one in your lover's eyes.
أنت الوحيدة في عيون العشاق
Gosh.
مهلاً
It's done.
لقد نجحت
I don't think anything is done.
كيف يمكن ذلك؟
The answer is obvious.
الجواب في الجواب
Hooks.
عقد؟
They are tent pegs.
هذا يسمى المسمار
They are not hooks. Can you do it?
ليس عقدًا، هل يمكنك فعل ذلك؟
Well.
لا
What do you mean?
ما معنى هل يمكن ذلك أم لا
Can't you see I'm almost done?
ألم تريني أنجزها على الفور؟
Do it if you can.
يمكنك فعلها
You do it.
أنت
Do it. I've prepared it for you.
تعال   لقد أعددت لك
-What are they doing? -Please.
ماذا تفعل
It'll be done soon.
سأنهي حالاً
Is there anything I can help with?
هل تحتاج إلى مساعدتي
No. It's almost done.
لا، انتهيت تقريباً
Good. Take him away.
من الجيد أن تأخذه بسرعة
Otherwise, we have to save him later.
وإلا سننقذه بعد قليل
What do you mean?
ماذا تقول؟
Smart. Come on.
أنت ذكي تعال
Go wash the vegetables.
اذهبي لغسل الخضروات
Your mom gave you 200 yuan when you were little
ألم تغسل الخضروات عندما كنت صغيراً؟
because you washed vegetables clean, right?
حتى غسل الخضروات
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Look. I knocked in the tent pegs.
انظر إلى المسمار
I assembled it.
‫لقد صنعتها‬
Now, the only thing I don't know
‫الشيء الوحيد الذي لا أعرفه الآن هو‬
is what this
هذا الشيء
is for.
ما هذا؟
It's for pulling out the tent pegs.
هذا مسمار على الأرض
Mr. Xiao, what a coincidence.
أيتها الطبيبة شياو يا لها من صدفة
It's not a coincidence.
يا لها من صدفة
I specially came here
أنا هنا خصيصًا
for you.
للبحث عنكم
Mr. Xiao. You just got discharged from the hospital.
دكتورة شياو لقد خرجت للتو من المستشفى
Go get some rest.
اذهبي للراحة
I'm fine.
أنا بخير
But if you are tired,
أنت
you can tell me.
يمكنك إخباري إذا كنت متعب
You can get some rest too.
يمكنك الذهاب للراحة
Orange, help me with his.
البرتقال ساعديني على تحمل هذا المكان
I'm flying.
لقد تطير
Cooperation is what matters when we pitch a tent.
بناء الخيمة يعتمد على التعاون
Then cooperate with me, understand?
يجب أن تتعاون معي، مفهوم؟
Then cooperate with me.
يجب أن تتعاون معي
Understand?
مفهوم؟
Left or right?
اليسار أم اليمين
What are you looking at?
إلى ماذا تنظر
Can't I take a break?
لا يمكن الاستراحة
No need.
لا داعي
You can carry this, right?
هل يمكنك حمل هذا
Easy.
استرخي
Have you watched Animal World?
هل رأيت عالم الحيوانات من قبل
What do you...
ماذا تعني؟
What Animal World?
أي عالم حيوان؟
Hey. What...
ما هذا؟
What animal?
أي حيوان؟
Is this the table you prepared?
هل هذه الطاولة التي أعددتها؟
Are these the chairs you mentioned?
هذا هو الكرسي الذي ذكرته
Look at them.
انظر إلى هذا الرجل
What a scene.
هذا مثير للإعجاب
Not that impressive.
لا بأس به
Hey.
مهلاً
You're working overtime too?
هل تعملين لساعات إضافية أيضاً؟
Yes.
نعم
Hey.
ماذا؟
Among the seeds you brought back,
ما أحضرته
how many do you think
كم تعتقد
can successfully grow into Dioscorea nipponica Makino?
يمكن تدريبها لبس البطاطس
I'm just responsible for sorting them out for Professor Song.
أنا فقط أساعد البروفيسور سونغ في ترتيب
I've given you and Xiao Jing
النتيجة المحددة
the specific results,
أنا
right?
أعطيتك أنت وشياو جينغ
I'm just afraid that
أخشى أن أصبح
I'm the kid who holds an empty pot.
الطفل الذي يحمل وعاء الزهور الفارغ
Besides, considering
والطبيب شياو
what happened to Mr. Xiao recently,
حدث شيء كبير مؤخرًا
I feel the pressure is all on me.
أشعر أن الضغط قد جلب لي
Do you want me to help you with something?
هل تريدني أن أساعدك؟
That's very kind of you.
هذا محرج جدا
Can you help me with the analysis
تحليل محلول الغذائية والالتربة المغذية
of the nutrient solution and nutrient soil?
ساعديني في صنعها
Okay.
حسنا
I'll give it to you when I come to work on Monday.
سأعطيك العمل يوم الاثنين
Professor.
بروفيسور
Hey, Dong.
شياو دونغ
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
I'm here to help Yang...
أنا أساعد يانغ
This kid...
هذا الطفل
Professor.
أيها الأستاذ
How is your health?
هل أنت بخير؟
I'm fine.
لا بأس
You saw the examination report, right?
ألم تري تقرير الفحص أيضًا؟
I'm good.
جيد جدا
It's easy to have a relapse.
من السهل تكرار هذا
You should rest well.
يجب أن ترتاحي
I will.
سوف أنتبه
Look at you guys.
انظروا إليكم
You don't even rest on weekends.
لم تستريحوا في عطلة نهاية الأسبوع
And you always ask me to rest.
ما زلت تطلب مني أن أستريح
Fine.
حسنا
I'm going to rest.
سأذهب للراحة
Be careful. Professor.
ببطء أيها الأستاذ
Okay.
حسنا
I'm leaving these to you.
سأتركه لكم
There are more.
هناك المزيد في الخلف
Get started.
هيا
You don't know how to do it?
أنت لا تستطيع
Why should I?
لماذا أفعل ذلك؟
Aren't you running a restaurant?
ألست تعمل في الفندق؟
Stores opening at night are not necessarily restaurants.
‫لا يجب أن يكون كل المطعم في المساء هو فندق‬
Yes. They could be night entertainment venues.
نعم هناك نوع آخر يسمى الملهى الليلي
They all sell snacks, right?
ألم يبيع الوجبات الخفيفة؟
The stores selling snacks are called snack stores,
‫الذي يبيع الوجبات الخفيفة يسمى متجر الوجبات الخفيفة‬
or snack shops.
يسمى أيضًا متجر صغير
What's the difference?
ما الفرق
There's a big difference.
فرق كبير
You must be hungry.
هل الجميع جائعون؟
Let me cook.
ما رأيك أن أطبخ؟
You?
أنت
Cook?
طبخ
What?
ماذا؟
You think I'll poison you?
هل يمكنني أن أسممك؟
It's possible.
‫فقط هناك احتمال قليلا
Orange, let me help you.
البرتقال سأساعدك
You can cook?
هل تعرف كيف تطبخ
No.
لا
Then you won't be alone even if you fail.
هكذا لن تفشل بمفردك
Even if we fail,
الفشل
it is the responsibility of the two of us.
سنتحمل المسؤولية معا
Then you should take the main responsibility.
عندئذ ستصبح كبش فداء
Okay.
حسنا
Which one do you like?
أي واحدة تفضلين؟
Let's start with chicken feet.
‫لنأكل أرجل الدجاج أولا‬
I love chicken feet.
أحب أرجل الدجاج
Like this.
هكذا
Be careful. Don't poke your hands.
ببطء لا تلمس يديك
One more.
مرة أخرى
Does it look like your hand?
هل هذا يبدو يدك؟
No.
لا
One more.
‫سلق أرجل الدجاج مرة أخرى‬
Chicken feet with fish tofu.
أرجل الدجاج مع التوفو السمك
Treasure in the palm.
كنز يديك
What is this? Treasure in the palm?
ما هذا؟
Treasure in the palm.
كنز السيطرة
Look.
انظر
This is
أنت
Dwelling in the Fuchun Mountains.
خريطة جبل فو تشون
What?
ماذا؟
You're indeed an artist.
أنت حقا فنان
You're special even when you are making food skewers.
‫لا يختلف عن الآخرين
I didn't even realize it myself.
لم أرى نفسي
I'm making another treasure in the palm for Smart.
سأصخر كنز السيطرة لأعطي الذكاء الأكل
Ouyang Yu.
‫أو يانغ يو
Come with me to get coal.
اذهب معي للحصول على الكربون
Let's go.
لنذهب
Kitty.
قطة قطة
What should I do?
ماذا نفعل؟
Why did you come back suddenly?
لماذا عدت فجأة
I regret it.
أنا نادم
Regret?
ندمت؟
Yes.
نعم
It's an important matter. You think I'll pretend nothing happened just because you regret it?
هذا الأمر المهم
Do you know how sad she was because of you?
هل تعرف كم هي حزينة من أجلك؟
I'll make it up to her.
سأعوضها
How?
كيف؟
Cry for her for three days and nights?
هل تبكين لأجلها لثلاثة أيام وليالي
Do you have a heart? Tell me.
هل لديك قلب
You can't deny that I'm also a carbon-based creature.
لا يمكنك إنكار أنني أيضًا مخلوقات الكربون
My heart is right here.
قلبي هنا
It's too late to regret.
لقد فات الأوان على الندم
Can't you see my relationship with Orange has improved a lot?
ألا ترى العلاقة بيني وبين البرتقال تطور بسرعة
Tonight,
الليلة
I will confess my love to her.
سأعبر لها مشاعري
Then I'll do my best to turn the tide.
سأبذل قصارى جهدي لإعادة الوضع
Let's wait and see.
‫لننتظر ونرى
Orange.
البرتقال
Mr. Xiao saved you.
الطبيب شياو أنقذك
And you accompanied him for so long.
لقد قمت بحمايته لفترة طويلة
Now he is here for you.
لماذا جاء إليك خصيصًا؟
Why are you cold to him?
أنت لست متحمسًا
This is a deal with the demon.
هذا شرط للتبادل مع الشيطان
You won't understand even if I tell you.
لن تفهم
Show yourself.
اخرج
Nephew?
ابن أخي
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
East, West, South, North, and Red. The good wine is in Shandong.
الشرق والشمال والغرب والغرب والجنوب والشمال والشرق والخمر الجيد في شاندونغ
Good.
لذيذ
One more glass.
كأس آخر
I'll count to three.
سأعد إلى ثلاثة
Let him sleep a little longer.
دعه ينام قليلا
Three.
ثلاثة
Two.
اثنان
Hi.
مرحباً
Aren't you drunk?
ألست ثملاً؟
What can I do for you?
هل يمكنني أن أفعل شيئاً لك؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Thank you.
شكرا
Everyone.
الجميع
Actually, I'm not good at these things at all.
في الواقع هذه ليست نقاط قوتي على الإطلاق
What I'm best at
أكبر نقاط قوتي
is making a fire.
هو إشعال النار
Can't you just sit quietly?
هل يمكنك الجلوس والهدوء قليلا
There will be something missing every time you move.
كل حركة تنقص شيئًا
Look, it's empty here.
‫انظر نحن فارغون‬
You heard her.
هذا ما قلته
Don't say I don't work
لا تتحدث عني
and only know eating.
تأكل فقط ولا تعمل
Stop running if you dare.
لا تهرب
Don't run.
لا تتحرك
I'm speechless.
شكرا جزيلا لك
You can't do things well, but you eat a lot.
لا يمكنك أن تفعل أي شيء
I'm cheap, right?
ألست رخيصا
Who asked you to choose me?
من سمح لك باختياري
Who asked you to come out?
من سمح لك بالخروج
Go back now.
عد الآن
I was worried that you are alone.
أخشى أن تكون وحيداً
So I came out to support you.
‫أتيت خصيصًا لدعمك‬
I can liven it up.
‫المسئولة عن الأجواء‬
Eat this.
تناولي واحدة
Xiaoxiao.
شياو شياو
Did you tell Xiao Jing
هل أخبرت شياو جينج
I'm here?
أنني هنا
Then tell me
أخبرني
who you'll choose
أو يانغ يو والمعلم شياو
between Ouyang Yu and Mr. Xiao.
أي واحد تختارين
What kind of question is this?
ما هذه المشكلة السيئة
I don't want to talk to you.
لا أهتم بك
Hey.
مهلاً.
Can we stop talking separately?
هل يمكننا التوقف عن الحديث عن أنفسنا؟
Let's play a game together.
لنلعب لعبة معا
Okay?
حسناً؟
Well.
هكذا
I'm not going to tell you the rules now.
لن أتحدث عن قواعد اللعبة
But listen.
لكن أقول لكم
The seating
مقعد هذه اللعبة
is very important in this game.
مهم جدا
Now, I'm going to
ثم أنا
make the seating arrangements
سأستخدم أسلوب علمي
in the most scientific way.
لمساعدتكم في ترتيب المقعد
That is,
‫ما هو؟‬
drawing lots.
سحب
This game is very exciting.
هذه اللعبة مثيرة للغاية
It's called
اسمه
"Curiosity
فضولي
Kills the Dog".
قتل الكلب
Let me tell you the rules first.
دعني أشرح قواعد هذه اللعبة أولا
For example,
على سبيل المثال
he asked me a question
إن ابن أخي الأكبر يسألني
in a secret way.
اسألني سؤالا
Everyone here may be the answer.
كل شخص هنا قد يكون الجواب
And I will use this
سأستخدم هذا الأصبع الصغير
to point at the answer.
لأعطي هذا الجواب
If you
‫إذا كان شخص ما في الموقع‬
are curious about the question,
‫فضول هذا السؤال‬
well,
جيد جدا
you have to drink a glass of the special drink I made.
أريد أن أشرب كأس خاص
Well.
بالطبع هذا
If you like it very much,
من يحبه أكثر
welcome to my bar.
أهلاً بكم في حانتي
You need to pay for it.
سأدفع ثمن النبيذ بنفسك سأدفع ثمن النبيذ بنفسك
Okay, let's
حسنًا فلنبدأ
get started.
لنبدأ
You are going to
شكل رجل أعمال خبيث
become an unscrupulous merchant.
قد شكلت
Shut up.
اخرس
What did he say?
ماذا قلت للتو؟
Nothing.
لا شيء
Wait.
انتظر
I want to know the question.
‫أريد أن أعرف السؤال‬
Oh my gosh.
يا إلهي
I didn't expect Mr. Xiao
لم أتوقع أن الطبيب شياو
is the best at livening up the atmosphere among us.
أن تكون الأفضل في إثارة الأجواء
You should learn from him.
يجب أن تتعلموا.
I'll pour the wine.
سأسكب النبيذ سأسكب النبيذ
Okay. Now,
‫حسناً التالي‬
I'm going to tell you the answer.
‫سأعلن الجواب‬
The question I asked Big Orange is
السؤال الذي سألته للتو عن البرتقال
who she thinks
‫هي تعتقد عندما كنت في المدرسة‬
was the most disobedient in school.
في المدرسة
Okay. I'm going to ask the next question.
حسنًا، سأسأل السؤال التالي
Xiaoxiao.
شياو شياو
You have to be honest.
ما نريده هو لعبة ضمير
Be honest. Honest.
لعبة ضمير ضمير
It's not you anyway.
لماذا لست أنت
I want to know.
أريد أن أعرف
I'll pour the wine.
سأسكب النبيذ سأسكب النبيذ
He's a real man.
رجل حقيقي
I didn't expect that.
لم أتوقع ذلك
The second question I asked Big Orange is
سؤالي الثاني عن البرتقال
who she thinks
‫هي تعتقد‬
has been asked for the phone number the most frequently by people of the opposite sex.
‫من الذي طلب رقم الهاتف من أجنبي أكثر
I told you.
لقد قلت
He is
هو
very boring.
ممل جدا
Am I boring?
هل أنا مملة؟
Next question.
السؤال التالي
I want to know.
أريد أن أعرف